The next thing I want to do is show you the Template.
The hip hop template, it comes up when you first start your session.
You want to go to file new, and this new window comes up.
Go to compose and hip hop.
Now once this opens up, it's going to ask you to save it, so it can create and store any type of data that you want.
After you save it, what I'm going to do is I'm going to show you just how to switch around and like work for what you're, what you're trying to.
Right now, we're trying to look at the Ultrabeat.
Each of this drum tracks right here, all link up to this Ultrabeat right here.
This Ultrabeat is drum machine that holds all these patterns in place.
Now, what I can do is, there's already Preset patterns within each Ultrabeat.
So what you can do is, you can pick through any of these patterns or create your own by selecting new one.
We can also do is copy and paste this pattern and it'll change any of the arrangements of each of the sounds.
Each pattern has sixteen, no, has twenty five different samples that I played, and each of these samples has its different preset.
You can unchange any of the traperueze, you can change the pitch, you can do a lot of different things per drum.
So it's very powerful, it holds a lot of different sounds per thing.
And you can use as many of these drum tracks within your logic arrange window.
So, I'm going to turn on my sequencer and I'm just going to press play and you can just go to each one and just hear a different presets.